compuplus.com 2013-05-02

# Computer Parts, GPS Navigation, and Digital Cameras @ Comp-U-Plus; 1.800.287.2323

## Privacy Statement for www.compuplus.com

Comp-U-Plus Direct has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to consumer privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for www.compuplus.com. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Additionally, your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart.

Our site's checkout process requires you to provide us with your contact, shipping, and financial information. This information is used for order fulfillment, and to keep you updated on the status of your order.  From time to time, we may present offers to you from third party partners, and we may share certain information with those third party partners. We will not share, rent or sell any personally identifiable information with any third party without your consent. 

## Security

All of your personal information is entered on our secure SSL server for your protection. 

## Correct/Update

If you would like to change any submitted customer information, you can send an email to [webmaster@compuplus.com](mailto:webmaster@compuplus.com) , or call Customer Service at 845-352-8100. 

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact  Jeff Franklin Comp-U-Plus Direct 20 Robert Pitt Dr. Monsey, NY 10952 webmaster@compuplus.com
